Kristen thank you so much for being here
do you remember where we met was in New
York or was it the Aspen Comedy Festival
my first memory of you is New York City
we were filming our half hour Comedy
Central specials it was you me and John
Mulaney and you were nice I was ok so
you've got a foggy memory we did meet at
the Aspen Comedy Festival that was
before the half hour were you won best
alternative comedian yeah and I was like
what I guess I was so busy winning that
I don't really remember you yeah yeah
you won best alternative Committee which
I think was an award they invented that
year I mean that's to piss me off I
think they just did invented it because
I blew everyone's mind so much because
of how alternative you were alternatives
gonna come back just like Nirvana was it
Nirvana alternative I had some bad news
for you about Nirvana Kurt Cobain is
dead but you could have a heart attack I
think oh is it a heart attack - it's
good
yeah yeah do you think that if I had one
best alternative comedian that year
instead of you that I would be a guest
on your show I'm wondering what you
think is alternative about your comedy
and that it's just different in that it
just follows a typical stand-up format
and you'd never play with the rules of
comedy or stand-up I think I would like
on the I'm them on the verge of
alternative you know I mean I have
alternative was a high school yeah I'd
still be alternative but I'm one of the
jocks in the alternative high school I
mean was you'd be like playing a
clarinet yeah um alright but did I was
trying to remember again if you won no I
didn't I'm gonna move on for the sake of
ratings yes
christen your Twitter bio says comedian
actress writer why that order well I
guess because when I started that
Twitter account I was doing comedy the
most stand-up um because I think I
started in 2009 but what I really wanted
to be
was an actress and I was doing just a
little bit of that and then I just added
writer
yeah just like throw people off makes
you seem smarter published yes you do
wrote it with my husband rich Blomqvist
and it's called the sexy book of sexy
sex and it is out of print and they will
not be making more copies I would love
to read it next question first and fill
in the blank
IMDB says your trademark is playing
sweet-natured
but blank characters woo I would say
sweet-natured but with an unexpected
storm on the horizon you change the
whole sentence just to make us believe
you don't be jiron IMDb unstable I was
told were sweet natured but unstable
characters mm-hmm and you failed I don't
think I failed I think I said the same
thing I'm unstable you think a storm is
stable I asked you to parallel park and
you got out of the car and ran away no
you asked me the parallel park and I let
my Tesla do it for me
I stand corrected
I have a question for you when you write
your comedy jokes hmm they're so good
mm-hmm do you think of the twist before
you write it or do you think that the
premise first and then just like
scramble your brain for the twist the
latter I think of the premise I think
how many different ways it can go and
then what's like the meanest most
unexpected it still makes sense way yeah
yeah you're great thank you
you're local one of the best alternative
comedians of all time about what you do
I think if I didn't exist if I hadn't
been born yeah
alternative comedy would not be a thing
you can have alternative comedy thank
you but it doesn't belong to you I would
like the award ha ha ha give it to you
[Music]